# **Edgars Puce**

#### **Personal Details**

Name: **Edgars Puce** Date of Birth: 25/12/1987

Nationality: Latvian (European Union)

Email: <u>puce.edgar@gmail.com</u>

Phone Number: +82 010-2959-4518

GitHub: <u>EdgarPuceGitHub</u> LinkedIn: <u>Edgars Puce LinkedIn</u>



### **Personal Statement**

I am a passionate developer with 5 years of experience, who loves to write code and solve problems. Coding is fun because you can create something new from nothing and see results very quickly. Sometimes I struggle to solve issues, but the more I try and fail, the more I can learn. And when I succeed, I feel proud of myself.

I have registered a business in Korea and can work as a contractor/freelancer/B2B. Available to work from 8:00 until 18:00 EET time.

# Work Experience

July 2021 ~ October 2023: 28Stone Consulting, Inc. Latvia/South Korea

**Position:** Developer **Responsibilities:** 

- Worked on video recording and face recognition application for 6 months. Technologies used: Python, Electron.
- Created custom views in WPF for vendor application for 6 months.
- Worked on an internal project for company employee CV editing and generation application 1+ year. Technologies used: Angular, C#, AWS Lambda, AWS Cognito, AWS DynamoDB.

#### April 2019 ~ June 2021: SEB Global Services, Riga, Latvia

**Position:** Developer **Responsibilities:** 

- Developed AML related scenarios (SQL queries)
- Developed and deployed to production reporting solution (Required by Swedish Financial Police)
- Maintained and improved developed reporting solution based on requirements
- Worked on UI part for developed reporting solution to make it available to other departments within the bank (React)
- Collaborate with other IT teams and product owners in Latvia and Sweden

# March 2018 ~ March 2019: SEB Global Services, Riga, Latvia

**Position:** Junior Developer

Responsibilities:

- Maintained and updated vendor systems
- Maintained and developed QlikView application
- Automated manual processes of product owners
- Collaborate with other IT teams and product owners in Latvia and Sweden

#### August 2015 ~ March 2017: Tint a Car Korea Co., Ltd., Gyeonggi-do, South Korea

**Position:** Assistant Manager

**Responsibilities:** 

- Translating reports and documents from Korean to English
- Communication with Head office in Australia
- Meeting with international partners
- Helping with marketing
- Market research

#### June 2012 – August 2014: Centra Convenience Co., Ltd., Dublin, Ireland

Position: Assistant Manager

**Responsibilities:** 

- Ordering products for the shop
- Training new staff
- Making reports for the Head Office (daily and weekly)
- Finance management and cash flow
- Meeting with sales representatives
- Running the shop on my own when manager is absent
- Staff management
- Working with software like Point Four, G.O.L.D and IRIS

## February 2008 – February 2011: Tele2 Shared Service Center, Riga, Latvia

**Position:** Billing Operations Specialist

Responsibilities:

- Responsible for running and monitoring daily operations (first line support) of billing and surrounding systems
- Ensure that processes are running smoothly and provide support to the local Billing offices in Tele2 countries in all Europe
- Resolve requests on demand and issues
- Communication with internal and external departments and Head Office in Sweden
- Carried out daily operational, monitoring and corrective functions within Billing Operations Team

### **Skills**

#### Hard skills:

- Programming: C#, SQL. Some experience with: Java, JavaScript (React, AngularJs), Python
- Tools: VS 2022, VS Code, SSMS, GitHub, Git Bash, JIRA, Postman, Confluence, QlikView
- Other: JSON, XML, API, xUnit. Some experience with: AWS (Lambda, Cognito, DynamoDB)
- Way of working: Agile, Scrum, Kanban, Program Increment (SAFe)
- Language skills: Russian, Latvian (Native), English (Fluent), Korean (TOPIK 2)

#### Soft skills:

- Great communication skills to build good relationship with customers
- Flexible regarding working hours and location
- Able to work under pressure and deliver results to deadlines
- Detail oriented
- Flexible and adaptable, able to work well individually and in a group
- Open minded and willing to learn
- Fast learner, loyal and reliable

#### **Education**

#### Riga Technical University 2006 - 2010 (Latvia)

Bachelor degree in Telecommunications